Guide to the Time Inc. records Bio files 3009.RG2
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. Bio files
Bulk, 1933-1992
1907-2015 (bulk 1933-1992)
3009.RG2
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
100.0 Linear feet
The Time Inc. Bio files document the careers of Time Inc. staff, non-staff closely associated with the company, and notable figures. This record group also includes the collection’s primary files on cofounder Briton Hadden.
Scope and Contents Note
The Time Inc. Bio files, sometimes known as name files, were assembled and maintained by the Time Inc. Archives and predominately document the careers of Time Inc. staff from board members (H. P. Davison) and company executives (John S. Martin, Ray Cave, Hedley Donovan, Elizabeth Valk Long) to administrative assistants. Time Inc. also kept files on non-staff closely associated with the company such as contracted writers, topical advisors, subjects of articles, and some family and former classmates of cofounders Henry R. Luce and Briton Hadden in relation to interviews during various history and biography projects. Furthermore, the files include artists, architects, and historical figures due to additions of files during a reorganization of the libraries and archives after the Time Warner and AOL merger. Time Inc. housed Bio files on especially important historical figures or staff files of significance separately in a safe. This includes the collection’s primary files on cofounder Hadden.
Contents consist of correspondence; memoranda regarding new hires, departing staff and other staffing changes; press releases; news clippings including obituaries; articles from the staff newsletters primarily F.Y.I.; articles or correspondent cables by or about staff; reports and comments on articles and books under consideration for publication; invitations to events; and speeches or other public remarks. Photographs and other photographic material, and audiovisual recordings of interviews, oral histories, and public speeches are present infrequently. Of note are interview transcripts of staff reminiscences from the Time Inc. history project undertaken by Celia Sugarman and Alex Groner in the 1950s and 1960s. Time cover artist files such as Boris Artzybasheff and Wiliam Oberhardt may contain original sketches and other artwork. Most folders that contain correspondence from cofounder Luce are stamped “H. R. Luce.” Copies of pre-1933 memoranda and correspondence from Luce occasionally occur throughout the Bio files. Empty folders are retained and noted.
Arrangement Note
Arranged alphabetically.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers.
Related Archival Materials Note
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. records. For information about the other record groups and for overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. records (MS3009).
Provenance
Gift from Time Inc. in 2015.
- Time Inc. Edit Staff (Partial List)
- A
- Abell, George [H.R. Luce]
- Abercrombie, Thomas
- Aboodi, Oded
- Abraham, Seth G.
- Abrams, Katherine: Pix & bio; Reminiscences; Misc [H.R. Luce]
  Scope and Contents Note
  Early Luce Secretary
- Abu, Said [H.R. Luce]
- Acoca, Miguel
- Abu Rish, Abu Said
- Abbott, Berenice
- Abbe, James E.
- Adam, Ruth
- Adams, Ansel: Pix & bio; Sketches
- Adams, Charles A.
- Adams, Eddie
- Adams, Edward T. (Eddie)
- Adams, John: Reminiscences; Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Adams, John (& Family Papers)
- Adams, Lewis G.: Reminiscences
- Adams, Robert
- Adams, Sherman
- Adams, Virginia
- Adler, Edward
- Adler, Mortimer J.
- Agee, James: Sketches; Misc [H.R. Luce]; Writings
- Aigner, Lucien: Misc
- Aikman, David
- Airey, Norman
- Ainslie, James Jr.: Pix & bio; Reminiscences
- Ainslie, Peter
- Aislin
- Ajemian, Robert: [H.R. Luce]
- Ajemian, Robert (Bob)
- Albers, Josef
- Alberse, James: Pix & Bio
- Alberse, James D.
- Albertson, Rachel: Reminiscences
- Alexander, Brooke
- Alexander, Charles: Pix & Bio
- Alexander, Roy: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Reminiscences; Pix & Bio
- Alexander, Shana: Reminiscences
- Alexander, Thomas W.
- Alger, Joseph: Pix & Bio; Reminiscences; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Allard, William Albert
- Allbritton, Joe L.
- Allen, Casey
- Allen, Jennifer (Jenny)
- Allen, Oliver
- Allen, Tom Chris: Pix & Bio; Misc
- Alley, Norman
- Allis, Sam
- Allis, Sam(uel)
- Allner, Walter
- Allner, Walter H.
- Almond, John: Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Alsop, Stewart
- Alvarrez (Bravo), Manuel
- Alves, Mary: Pix & Bio [Empty]; Reminiscences; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Ambrose, William V.
- Ames, Jr., Wilmer C.
- Amfitheatrof, Eril
- Amin, Mohamed
- Ammarell, Ray: Pix & Bio; Reminiscences
- An, Pham Xuan
- Anastasia
- Anderson, Alan H.
- Anderson, Christopher P.
- Anderson, Donald E.
- Anderson, Erika
- Anderson, Harlan
- Anderson, Kurt: Bio & Pix
- Anderson, Kurt B.
- Anderson, Peter
- Andrews, Burt
- Angell, William: Pix & bio; Reminiscences
- Angelo, Bonnie
- Angeloff, Sam A.
- Angeloff, Sam
- Angier, Natalie
- Angle, Richard (Chip)
- Ankerson, Robert
- Annigoni, Pietro
- Anson, Robert
- Anson, Robert Sam
- Appel, Allen
- Arbus, Diane
- Ardrey, Robert
- Arias, Ron
- Arlen, Michael
- Arlen, Michael J.
- Armstrong, Elizabeth: Misc; Reminiscences
- Armstrong, Richard A.
- Armstrong, Richard (Dick)
- Arnold, Eve
- Arnold, Stuard: Pix & bio
- Arnold, William R.
- Aron, Bill
- Artandi, George
- Artzybasheff, Boris: Misc
- Asher, Mrs. John
- Ashmore, Harry
- Astor, Gerald
- Atget, Eugene
- Atkins, Ollie
- Attinger, Joelle
- Atwater, James D.
- Auchincloss, Douglas: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio; Reminiscences; Speeches
- Auer, Bernhard M(achold)
- Auer, Bernhard: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]; Speeches; Reminiscences
- Aurelio, Richard
- Austell, Rhett: Pix & bio; Reminiscences; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Austin, John
- Avedon, Richard
- Avirgan, Tony
- Aymar, Gordon C.
- Azzi, Robert J.
- BA
- Babcock, Franklin Lawrence: Pix & bio
- Babcox, Peter C.
- Babington-Smith, Constance
- Bach, Clarence Abel
- Bach, Julian: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio
- Bach, Richard
- Bachman, Harriet
- Bachrach, Bradford
- Bachrach, Louis Fabian
- Backe, John D.
- Bacon, Dorothy
- Bacon, Francis: Sketches
- Bacon, James
- Badger, Priscilla
- Badger, Sherwin: [H.R. Luce]
- Bagdikian, Ben Haig: Pix & bio
- Bailey, David
- Bailey, Ron
- Bailey, Truman E.
- Bailey, Wes: "Legal"(Throw Away Some Day!); Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Baker, Alfred T. (III) Bob
- Baker, A.T.: Pix & bio; Misc
- Baker, Edgar R.: Pix & bio; Reminiscences; Speeches; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Baker, Ernest Hamlin
- Baker, Richard
- Balfour, Honor: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Balfour, Victoria
- Ball, Audrey
- Ball, George
- Ball, Robert (Bob)
- Ball, Robert P.
- Ballard, David W.: Pix & bio
- Balliett, Carl James: Pix & bio
- Baltermants, Dmitri
- Balterman, Lee
- Banks, Louis: Reminiscences [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio; Speeches & Writings, Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Banta, Kenneth W.
- Barco, James W.
- Bargo, Jean: Reminiscences
- Baring-Gould, William: Pix & bio; Speeches
- Barkham, John Michael: Pix & bio; Misc
- Barlett, Donald L.
- Barlow, Howard: Reminiscences
- Barnes, Alice: [H.R. Luce]
- Barnes, Bernard: Reminiscences; Misc [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio; Speeches
- Barnes, Ed
- Barnes, Edward J. (Ed)
- Barnes, Edward L(arrabee)
- Barnes, Kurt
- Barnes, William
- Barnet, Bruce
- Barnet, Bruce A.
- Barnett, Amy DuBois
- Barnett, Lincoln: Pix & bio; Misc; Reminiscences
- Barney, Tina
- Barr, Allen: Files
- Barr, Allen M.
- Barr, Don: Pix & bio
- Barr, Don(ald) J
- Barr, Robert
- Barr, Robert C.
- Barrett, Laurence I.: Sketches
- Barreau, Paul: [Empty]
- Barthel, Joan
- Barthelme, Marion Knox
- Barton, Bruce
- Barton, Bruce Jr.
- Barzini, Luigi
- Barzun, Jacques
- Basch, Peter
- Bassett, Margaret Byrd: Reminiscences, Misc [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio
- Basso, Edna: Reminiscences; Pix & bio
- Baughman, J. Ross
- Bavagnoli, Carlo
- Bayer, Ann
- BE
- Beahrs, Richard
- Beal, John Robinson: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Beall, Bill (WM. C.)
- Beals, Jessie Tarbok
- Bear, Charles B.: Misc [H. R. Luce]; Pix & bio
- Bear, Charles A.: Misc
- Beard, John: Reminiscences; Pix & bio
- Beardwood, John: [H.R. Luce]
- Beardwood, Roger
- Beaton, Sir Cecil: Sketches
- Beaty, Jonathan C.
- Beatty, Frank
- Beauchamo, Anthony
- Beausacq, Countess Ingeborg de
- Becher, Hilla
- Beck, John
- Beckert, Patricia
- Beckwith, Carol
- Beckwith, David
- Beebe, Lloyd
- Beech, Keyes
- Behar, Richard: Pix & bio
- Behr, Edward
- Belair, Felix: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Belden, Jack: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio
- Bel Geddes, Norman: [H.R. Luce]
- Belknap, Walter: Reminiscences; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Bell, Daniel: [H.R. Luce]
- Bell, James: Pix & bio; Speeches & writings; Reminiscences; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Bell, James A. (Jim): Sketches
- Bello, Francis: Pix & bio; Misc
- Bellocq, E. J
- Benchley, Robert
- Bender, William
- Bender, William (Bill)
- Benet, Stephen Vincent: Misc
- Benham, Frederick Darius: Reminiscences
- Benjamin, Evelyn
- Benjamin, Robert
- Bennett, Walter: Pix & bio
- Bernard, Walter
- Benney, Isabel: Pix & bio; Reminiscences
- Benson, Harry: Pix & bio; Sketches; Reminiscences [ Life Anniv. 1986], Reminiscences [Loengard Interview 1/10/92]
- Benson, Richard M.
- Bentkowski, Tom
- Bentley, Howard: Pix & bio
- Benton, Nicholas
- Benton, Nicholas (Nick)
- Benton, William
- Beny, (Wilfred) Roloff
- Berdan, John Milton
- Bere, James F.
- Beretty, Dominique
- Bergamini, David: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce)
- Berges, Marshall: Pix & bio
- Berges, Marshall: Reminiscences; Misc
- Berghash, Mark
- Berks, Robert
- Berle, Adolph
- Berman, Bruce
- Berman, Peggy T.
- Bermingham, Don: Pix & bio
- Bernays, Edward L.
- Bernhard, Arnold: Reminiscences
- Bernstein, Carl
- Bernstein, Elliott
- Bernstein, Lester: Pix & bio; Misc
- Bernstein, Lou
- Bernstein, Peter W(alter)
- Bernstein, Richard
- Berry, John F
- Berry, John M
- Berry, Madeleine
- Beshoar, Barron: Pix & bio; Misc
- Bethke, Amos: Pix & bio
- Bettmann, Otto L
- Bewkes, Jeff
- BI
- Biddle, George
- Bidwell, Seth: [H.R. Luce]
- Bigelow, E(ugene) Thayer (Jr)
- Bigelow, Hugh: Reminiscences
- Bigelow, Thayer
- Billings, Dick
- Billings, Henry: Pix & bio
- Billings, John Shaw: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]; Reminiscences, Reminiscences [1937 & before]; Reminiscences [1938 & 1939]; Reminiscences [1940 & 1941]; Reminicences [1942 & 1944]; Reminiscences [1945 & 1946]; Reminiscences [1947 & later]; Writings
- Billock, John
- Binford, Julien: Pix & bio; Misc
- Binning, Thomas W.
- Binzen, Bill
- Biondi, Frank: Speeches
- Biondi, Frank J. (Jr.)
- Bing, Ilse
- Bingham, Howard
- Bipart, Herbert: Pix & bio
- Bipart, C. Herbert: Reminiscences
- Birnbaum, Jeffrey H.
- Birnbaum, Jesse
- Birns, Jack: Pix & bio; Reminiscences [Loengard Interview 8/14/93]; Writings
- Bischof, Werner
- Bischoff, Sam
- Bishop, William E
- BL
- Black, Howard: Pix & bio; Reminiscences; Speeches, Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Black, Len: [H.R. Luce]
- Black, Shirley Temple
- Blacker, Stephen M
- Blair, Clay: Pix & bio
- Blair, Clay Jr.: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Speeches; Sketches
- Blair, Patricia
- Blake, Peter
- Blake, Rebecca
- Blashall, John: Pix & bio
- Blaylock, William D.
- Blaylock, William (Bill)
- Blecha, Bonnie
- Blitzer, Victor W.
- Bloch, Kurt: Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Block, Gay
- Blom, Benjamin
- Blossfeldt, Karl
- Blum, Robert: Reminiscences
- Blundew, Edmund
- Blynn, Bryce (Buzz)
- BO
- Bodine, A Aubrey
- Boenzi, Neal
- Boeth, Margaret (Sissy)
- Boggs, Timothy A.
- Bohrod, Aaron: Pix & bio; Misc
- Bolander, Tage
- Bolte, Gisela
- Bolte, Gisela
- Boltin, Lee
- Bolwell, Edwin (Ted)
- Boncenne, Felix
- Bonfante, Jordan
- Bonnay, Charles
- Bonney, Therese
- Bonniwell, Katherine
- Bonniwell, Katherine M
- Bonventre, Peter: Pix & bio
- Bookman, George: [H.R. Luce]
- Booth, Cathy
- Booth, Karen Burger
- Borgzinner, Jon
- Borman, Martin
- Borrell, John
- Bosshard, Walter
- Boulat, Pierre
- Bourdin, Guy
- Bourges, Fernand
- Bourke-White, Margaret
  Includes a vinyl disc.
- Bourne, Dorothea
- Bourne, Russell
- Bowen, Ezra: Pix & bio
- Bowen, William: Pix & bio
- Bowles, Chester
- Bowra, Sir Maurice
- Boyce, Joe
- Boyce, Joseph (Joe)
- Boyd, Robert: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio
- Boyd, Russell
- Boyer, Edward J.
- Boyle, John
- Boyle, John W.
- BR
- Brack, Dennis
- Brack, Reginald K. Jr.: Pix & bio; Speeches [1980-1986]; Speeches [1987]; Speeches [1988]; Speeches [1989]; Speeches [1990-]
- Bracken, Brendan: Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Branden, Elisabeth
- Bradbury, Ray
- Bradbury, Will
- Bradshaw, D.Y.: Reminiscences
- Brady, Kathleen
- Braestrup, Peter
- Bragonier, Reginald Jr. (III ?)
- Brandt, Bert
- Brandt, Bill
- Brassai
- Braun, Ernest
- Bravagnoli, Carlo
- Brean, Herbert: Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Breckenfeld, Gurney: [H.R. Luce]; Speeches
- Breckinridge, Mary Marvin
- Brellis, Dean: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Brennan, Francis: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio; Reminiscences
- Brennan, Francis E. (Hank)
- Breu, Giovanna
- Breseman, Herbert L.
- Bressler, Richard J.
- Breves, Iris Turner: [H.R. Luce]
- Brew, Douglas James
- Brewster, Daniel Jr.
- Brewster, W. Rice
- Brice, A. Donald: [H.R. Luce]
- Bridges, Marilyn
- Brigham, Robert
- Brigham, Robert (Bob)
- Brill, Steven
- Brine, Ruth
- Brinker, Robert C
- Brinkley, Alan
- Brinkley, Alan
- Brinkley, William: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Bristol, Horace: Pix & bio; Reminiscences [Loengard Interview 8/13/93]
- Britt, Glenn A.
- Brock, Ray: [H.R. Luce]
- Broidy, Gerald: Pix & bio
- Brockaw, Ann Clare
- Bronowski, Jacob
- Bronner, Fred(erick) V(oorhees)
- Brook, Alexander
- Brooke, Sylvia (Lady)
- Brooks, John: Pix & bio
- Brosan, Roberto
- Brosnahan, Vincent J.
- Brower, Brock
- Brown, Brian
- Brown, Dale M
- Brown, Donald F.
- Brown, Earl: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Brown, Francis
- Brown, Heywood
- Brown, Joe David: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Brown, Roger
- Brown, Scott
- Brown, Tracy: Pix & bio
- Brownstein, Vivian
- Bruck, Connie
- Brule, Tyler
- Brumbaugh, David Willis: Pix & bio; Reminiscences; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Brumbaugh, David
- Bruner, Jerome S.
- Bruns, Bill
- Bryan, Julien H.
- Bryant, Cleill
- Bryson, Gary
- Bryson, John
- Brzezinski, Zbigniew
- BU
- Buba, Mrs. Joy
- Bubley, Esther
- Buchanan, Al Jr.
- Bucher, Lloyd
- Buchwald, Art
- Bucker, Rinker
- Buckham, Alfred G.: Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Buckley, William F. Jr.
- Buckhout, Clay
- Buckley, R.M.: Bio; Speeches
- Buckhout, Clay: Pix & bio; Speeches; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Buell, Raymond Leslie: Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Buffet, Bernard
- Buhagiar, Mario
- Bullaty, Sonja
- Bullock, Wynn
- Bunzel, Peter
- Buranelli, Prosper
- Burchard, Marshall
- Burchett, Wilfred
- Burck, Charles: Pix & bio
- Burck, Gilbert: Pix & bio
- Burckhardt, Rudy
- Burden, Shirley C
- Burdick, Eugene
- Bureau, Henri
- Burger, Elva: Reminiscences
- Burgheim, Richard: Pix & bio
- Burgheim, Richard (Dick)
- Burke, Don: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Burke, James Cobb: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Burke, James
- Burkhalter, Vernon
- Burnett, David
- Burnett, Leo
- Burns, James Mac Gregor
- Burrell, Fred
- Burrows, Barbara Baker: Pix & bio
- Burrows, Larry: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio; Sketches
- Burrows, Barbara Baker (Bobbie)
- Burrows, Vicki
- Burstein, Patricia
- Burt, David
- Burtin, Will: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio
- Burton, Sandra
- Busch, Niven: Pix & bio; Reminiscences; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Busch, Noel F.: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]; Writings
- Bush, Vannevar
- Butler, Peter
- Butterfield, Alfred Coe
- Butterfield, Roger: Pix & bio; Reminiscences; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Button, Sally
- Butts, Virginia: [H.R. Luce]
- Byers, Margery
- Bylinsky, Gene: Pix & bio
- Byrd, Richard E. (Admiral): Misc
- Byron, Christopher M.
- Byron, Christopher (Chris)
- CA
- Cagnoni, Romano
- Cain, Harry P.: Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Calcraft, Eric
- Caldwell, Erskine
- Calhoun, Millard Fillmore: Pix & bio; Reminiscences
- Calkins, Deborah Hathaway: Pix & bio
- Calkins, Deborah: Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Calkins, Deborah Hathaway: Reminiscences
- Calhoun, Millard Fillmore: Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Callahan, Harry
- Callahan, Tom
- Callas, Maria
- Callaway, Llewellyn L. (Pete): Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Callaway, L(lewellyn) L(ine) (Pete) Jr.
- Camacho, Mathilde
- Cameron, Denis
- Cameron, Gail
- Cameron, Mrs. Julia Margaret
- Campbell, Alexander: Pix & bio
- Campbell, Alexander (Alec)
- Campbell, Eldon
- Campbell, Jeanne (Lady)
- Campbell, Jule
- Campbell, Jule: [Empty]
- Campbell, Robert (Bob)
- Campbell, Rodney
- Campbell, Ronald N.
- Canby, Henry Seidel
- Canby, Henry Seidel
- Canova, John
- Cant, Gilbert
- Cantwell, John
- Cantwell, Robert: Misc [H.R. Luce]l Reminiscences; Pix & bio
- Capa, Cornwell: [H.R. Luce]; Reminiscences [Loengard Interviews 10/25/93]
- Capa, Robert: Pix & bio
- Capa, Robert: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Sketches [1945-1966]; Sketches [1967-]
- Capell, Daniel
- Caponigro, Paul
- Capp, Al: [H.R. Luce]
- Carey, A.M.: Pix & bio [H.R. Luce]
- Carey, W. Henry: Pix & bio
- Carey, Robert: [H.R. Luce]
- Carlin, Vince
- Carlson, Arnold W.: Pix & bio; Reminiscences; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Carlson, David
- Carlson, Larry
- Carlson, Margaret
- Carmichael, Thomas N.
- Carney, James F.
- Carpenter, Chapin
- Carpenter, Harry: Reminiscences
- Carr, William B.: Pix & bio; Reminiscences
- Carraro, Mauro
- Carroll, Jean: Reminiscences
- Carroll, Kathleen
- Carroll, Thomas E (Tom)
- Carry, Peter
- Carson, Lorraine
- Carter, E. Graydon
- Carter, John Franklin: Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Carter, Malcom N
- Carter, Ovie
- Cartier-Bresson, Henri: Pix & bio; Sketches [1943-]
- Cary, Joyce
- Casals, Pablo
- Case, Stephen
- Casey, Beatrice
- Cassandre, A.M
- Casson, Hugh: Pix & bio
- Castro, Janice
- Castro, Juana
- Castronovo, Val
- Cate, Ben: Pix & bio
- Cate, Benjamin W.
- Cathcart, Emelda
- Cathcart, Noble: Reminiscences
- Catton, Bruce
- Caughman, Susan
- Cave, Ray: Sketches
- Cavett, Dick
- Cecil, Baron Richard Valentine
- Cellario, Alberto R.: Pic & bio
- Cellario, Alberto
- Censor, Walters: Pix & bio
- Cerf, Edward: Pix & bio
- Cerf, Edward: Misc
- CH
- Chabrier, Yvonne V.
- Chace, Lynwood M.
- Chaliapin, Boris: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Chaliapin Family
- Chamberlain, John Rensselaer: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Chamberlain, John
- Chamberlain Samuel: (Diaries) [H.R. Luce]
- Chamberlin, Anne NChamberlin, Anne Nevin: Pix & bio [H.R. Luce]evin: Pix & bio [H.R. Luce]
- Chambers, Andrea
- Chambers, Robert Augustus: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio
- Chambers, Robert W
- Chambers, Whittaker: Hiss Trial [Aug-Dec, 1948][Wash. Bus. Coverage]; Hiss Trial [May-June 15, 1949][Wash. Bus. Coverage]; Hiss Trial [June 16-July, 1949][Wash. Bus. Coverage]; Hiss Trial [Nov-Dec., 1949][Wash. Bus. Coverage]; Hiss Trial [Jan-March, 1950][Wash. Bus. Coverage]; Publicity; Pix & bio; Hiss Trial [Misc]; Sketches
- Champlin, Charles: [H.R. Luce]
- Chandir, Riza: [H.R. Luce]
- Chan, David
- Chandler, David L(eon)
- Chandoha, Walter
- Chang, S(ungyung)
- Channing, William Ellery: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Chapelle, Anthony (Tony)
- Chapelle, Dickie
- Chapin, James
- Chapin, Robert: Pix & bio
- Chapman, Bert: Pix & bio; Reminiscences
- Chapman, Donald I
- Chapman, Helen Bushell: Reminiscences
- Chase, Merrill
- Chase, Nancy
- Chasteney, Robert W.: Pix & bio [H.R. Luce]; Reminiscences
- Cheek, Jay W.
- Chelminski, Rudolph (Rudi?)
- Cherichetti, Marie
- Chiang Kai-Shek, Madame
- Chiang, Oscar
- Chiapel, Tom
- Chickering, William H: Pix & bio; Misc; Writings
- Chiu, Eileen
- Chiu, Tony
- Chow, T.L.: Reminiscences
- Christo
- Christopher, Robert C.: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Chu, Valentin
- Chubb, Philip
- Church, Frank E. (Al): Pic & bio; Reminiscences; Speeches
- Church, George J
- Church, George
- Chwast, Seymour
- Ciampi, Elgin
- Ciano, Robert
- Cisneros, Maria Luisa
- CL
- Clarity, Ed
- Clark, Champ (II)
- Clark, Marsh
- Clark, Edgar
- Clark, Edward: Pix & bio; Reminiscences [Life Anniv. 1986]
- Clard, Ed: Reminiscences [Loengard Interview 11/3/1993]
- Clark, Joe
- Clark, Marsh
- Clarke, Fred
- Clarke, Gerald
- Clarke, Kenneth E.: Pix & bio
- Clarkson, Rich
- Claude
- Clayton, Al
- Clayton, Bernard Jr.: Pix & bio
- Cleeland, David: Bio
- Clergue, Lucien
- Cleland, Thomas M.: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio; Reminiscences
- Cleveland, Harlan
- Cleveland, Robert
- Clifford, Garry
- Clive, Robert
- Cloud, Stanley W.
- Cloud, Stanley
- Clurman, Richard: Pix & bio; Trips; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Clurman, Richard M (Dick): Sketches; Speeches
- Clurman, Shirley
- Cobbs, James W.
- CO
- Coburn, Alvin Langdon
- Coburn, Bob
- Cochrane, Robertson (Bob)
- Cochran, Jacqueline
- Cockburn, Claud: Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Cocks, Jay
- Codiroli, Joe
- Coffey, Joe
- Coffey, Richard E.: Pix & bio; Speeches
- Coffey, Richard E.
- Coffin, Patricia
- Cohen, Alan N.
- Coggin, Dan
- Cohen, Fred
- Cohen, Jerry
- Cohen, Mark
- Cohen, Wolfe
- Cole, David
- Cole, Henry B.
- Coleman, Jacqueline (Jackie)
- Collins, John
- Collins, Joseph J.
- Collier, John Jr.
- Collum, Charles
- Colson, Bill
- Colt, George Howe
- Colvin, Geoffrey
- Comarow, Avery
- Comarow, Avery
- Commons, William W.: Pix & bio
- Comte, Gilbert: Pix & bio
- Conant, Howell (Hal)
- Conant, James Richards: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Conboy, Brian
- Connell, Will
- Connelly, Mrs Joseph (Dolly)
- Connelly, Julie
- Connery, Donald: Pix & bio; Writigs; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Connery, Don(ald) S
- Connolly, Cyril
- Connolly, Lucille: Reminiscences
- Connolly, Marie: Reminiscences
- Constable, Anne
- Constable, George
- Constable, Rosalind
- Conway, William J.
- Converse, Gordon N.
- Cooil, Kathleen
- Cook, Eugene
- Cook, Jess
- Cooke, Alistair
- Cooke, Dwight: Reminiscences
- Cooke, Jerry
- Copage, Eric V
- Copps, Edwin
- Cordtz, Daniel
- Corliss, Richard
- Cornyn, Stan
- Corr, Joseph E. Jr.
- Cort, David: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio; Reminiscences
- Cory, Chris(topher)
- Cosindas, Marie
- Costa, Joseph (Joe)
- Coste, Henri
- Coster, Gordon
- Costiglio, Peter: Pix & bio
- Cotler, Sheldon [H.R. Luce]
- Cottrell, Laurence
- Coughlan, John Robert: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Coughlan, Robert (John)
- Coupon, William
- Coutu, D(iane) L
- Cowap, Agnes: Reminiscences
- Cowell, Theodore (Ted)
- Cowin, Robert: Misc; Reminiscences
- Cowles, Gardner: Misc
- Cowles, John: Misc
- Coy, Wayne: Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Coyle, Eugene F (Gene)
- Coyle, Joseph
- Cox, Winston H. (Tony)
- Cozzens, James Gould: Writings
- CR
- Cozzens, James Gould: Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Craig, Thomas
- Crandall, Robert S
- Crandell, John U.
- Crane, Arnold H.
- Crane, Ralph
- Crankshaw, Edward
- Crawford, Clare
- Crawford, Marc
- Creedman, Michael
- Crichton, Andy (Andrew)
- Crider, James: Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Crider, John H.: Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Cronin, Mary
- Cross, Richard
- Crovello, William
- Crowe, Phillip K.: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio
- Crowley, James G.: [H.R. Luce]
- Crowley, John J.
- Crowther, Geoffrey: Misc
- Crutcher, Lawrence M.
- Crutcher, Lawrence M (Larry)
- Cudahy, John
- Cunningham, Emory
- Cunningham, Imogen
- Cuomo, Ralph J.
- Curran, John: Pix & bio
- Curran, John J.
- Current, William R.
- Curtis, Gregory
- Cushing, Frank (Cush)
- Cutler, Elliott C.
- Czapnik, Sheldon: Pix & bio
- Czermanski, Zdislaw: Pix & bio; Misc
- DA
- Dahl, Patricia Neal
- Dahl-Wolfe, Mrs. Louise
- Daley, Marilyn G.
- Daly, Robert A.
- Dandridge, Frank
- Danforth, Kenneth C
- Dangerfield, George: Pix & bio
- Daniel, Carlyle C.
- Daniels, Jonathan
- Daniels, George (Gus)
- Daniels, Judith: Reminiscences [Life Anniv. 1986]
- D'Anjou, Rene
- Darby, Edwin Wheeler: Pix & bio
- Darby, Eileen
- Darrach, Henry Bradford: Pix & bio
- Darrach, Brad
- Dater, Judy
- Dauman, Henri
- Davenport, John: Pix & bio; Writings; Misc [H.R. Luce]; Sketches
- Davenport, Mrs Russell
- Davenport, Russell W.: Pix & bio; Speeches, Misc; Reminiscences; Writings
- Davenport, Russell W(heeler) (Mitch)
- David-Neel, Alexandra
- Davidson, Bruce
- Davidson, Ralph: Files & Archives
- Davidson Ralph P.: Sketches; Pix & bio; Speeches [1977-1980]; Speeches [1973-1976]; Speeches [1967-1972]; Speeches [1981]; Speeches [1982]; Speeches [1983]; Speeches [1984]; Speeches [1985 & later]; Trips